3Com Corp
3M Company
A.G. Edwards Inc.
Abbott Laboratories
Abercrombie & Fitch Co.
ABM Industries Incorporated
Ace Hardware Corporation
ACT Manufacturing Inc.
Acterna Corp.
"Adams Resources & Energy, Inc."
"ADC Telecommunications, Inc."
Adelphia Communications Corporation
"Administaff, Inc."
Adobe Systems Incorporated
Adolph Coors Company
"Advance Auto Parts, Inc."
"Advanced Micro Devices, Inc."
"AdvancePCS, Inc."
"Advantica Restaurant Group, Inc."
The AES Corporation
Aetna Inc.
"Affiliated Computer Services, Inc."
AFLAC Incorporated
AGCO Corporation
"Agilent Technologies, Inc."
Agway Inc.
Apartment Investment and Management Company
"Air Products and Chemicals, Inc."
"Airborne, Inc."
"Airgas, Inc."
AK Steel Holding Corporation
"Alaska Air Group, Inc."
Alberto-Culver Company
"Albertson's, Inc."
Alcoa Inc.
Alleghany Corporation
"Allegheny Energy, Inc."
Allegheny Technologies Incorporated
"Allergan, Inc."
"ALLETE, Inc."
Alliant Energy Corporation
"Allied Waste Industries, Inc."
Allmerica Financial Corporation
The Allstate Corporation
ALLTEL Corporation
"The Alpine Group, Inc."
"Amazon.com, Inc."
AMC Entertainment Inc.
American Power Conversion Corporation
Amerada Hess Corporation
AMERCO
Ameren Corporation
America West Holdings Corporation
"American Axle & Manufacturing Holdings, Inc."
"American Eagle Outfitters, Inc."
"American Electric Power Company, Inc."
American Express Company
"American Financial Group, Inc."
American Greetings Corporation
"American International Group, Inc."
American Standard Companies Inc.
"American Water Works Company, Inc."
AmerisourceBergen Corporation
"Ames Department Stores, Inc."
Amgen Inc.
"Amkor Technology, Inc."
AMR Corporation
AmSouth Bancorp.
"Amtran, Inc."
Anadarko Petroleum Corporation
"Analog Devices, Inc."
"Anheuser-Busch Companies, Inc."
Anixter International Inc.
AnnTaylor Inc.
"Anthem, Inc."
AOL Time Warner Inc.
Aon Corporation
Apache Corporation
"Apple Computer, Inc."
Applera Corporation
"Applied Industrial Technologies, Inc."
"Applied Materials, Inc."
"Aquila, Inc."
ARAMARK Corporation
"Arch Coal, Inc."
Archer Daniels Midland Company
Arkansas Best Corporation
"Armstrong Holdings, Inc."
"Arrow Electronics, Inc."
"ArvinMeritor, Inc."
Ashland Inc.
Astoria Financial Corporation
AT&T Corp.
Atmel Corporation
Atmos Energy Corporation
Audiovox Corporation
"Autoliv, Inc."
"Automatic Data Processing, Inc."
"AutoNation, Inc."
"AutoZone, Inc."
Avaya Inc.
Avery Dennison Corporation
Avista Corporation
"Avnet, Inc."
"Avon Products, Inc."
Baker Hughes Incorporated
Ball Corporation
Bank of America Corporation
"The Bank of New York Company, Inc."
Bank One Corporation
"Banknorth Group, Inc."
Banta Corporation
"Barnes & Noble, Inc."
Bausch & Lomb Incorporated
Baxter International Inc.
BB&T Corporation
The Bear Stearns Companies Inc.
"Beazer Homes USA, Inc."
"Beckman Coulter, Inc."
"Becton, Dickinson and Company"
Bed Bath & Beyond Inc.
"Belk, Inc."
Bell Microproducts Inc.
BellSouth Corporation
Belo Corp.
"Bemis Company, Inc."
"Benchmark Electronics, Inc."
Berkshire Hathaway Inc.
"Best Buy Co., Inc."
Bethlehem Steel Corporation
"Beverly Enterprises, Inc."
"Big Lots, Inc."
BJ Services Company
"BJ's Wholesale Club, Inc."
The Black & Decker Corporation
Black Hills Corporation
"BMC Software, Inc."
The Boeing Company
Boise Cascade Corporation
"Borders Group, Inc."
BorgWarner Inc.
Boston Scientific Corporation
Bowater Incorporated
Briggs & Stratton Corporation
"Brightpoint, Inc."
"Brinker International, Inc."
Bristol-Myers Squibb Company
"Broadwing, Inc."
"Brown Shoe Company, Inc."
Brown-Forman Corporation
Brunswick Corporation
"Budget Group, Inc."
Burlington Coat Factory Warehouse Corporation
"Burlington Industries, Inc."
Burlington Northern Santa Fe Corporation
Burlington Resources Inc.
C. H. Robinson Worldwide Inc.
Cablevision Systems Corp
Cabot Corp
"Cadence Design Systems, Inc."
Calpine Corp.
Campbell Soup Co.
Capital One Financial Corp.
Cardinal Health Inc.
Caremark Rx Inc.
Carlisle Cos. Inc.
Carpenter Technology Corp.
Casey's General Stores Inc.
Caterpillar Inc.
CBRL Group Inc.
CDI Corp.
CDW Computer Centers Inc.
CellStar Corp.
Cendant Corp
Cenex Harvest States Cooperatives
Centex Corp.
CenturyTel Inc.
Ceridian Corp.
CH2M Hill Cos. Ltd.
Champion Enterprises Inc.
Charles Schwab Corp.
Charming Shoppes Inc.
Charter Communications Inc.
Charter One Financial Inc.
ChevronTexaco Corp.
Chiquita Brands International Inc.
Chubb Corp
Ciena Corp.
Cigna Corp
Cincinnati Financial Corp.
Cinergy Corp.
Cintas Corp.
Circuit City Stores Inc.
Cisco Systems Inc.
"Citigroup, Inc"
Citizens Communications Co.
CKE Restaurants Inc.
Clear Channel Communications Inc.
The Clorox Co.
CMGI Inc.
CMS Energy Corp.
CNF Inc.
Coca-Cola Co.
Coca-Cola Enterprises Inc.
Colgate-Palmolive Co.
Collins & Aikman Corp.
Comcast Corp.
Comdisco Inc.
Comerica Inc.
Comfort Systems USA Inc.
Commercial Metals Co.
Community Health Systems Inc.
Compass Bancshares Inc
Computer Associates International Inc.
Computer Sciences Corp.
Compuware Corp.
Comverse Technology Inc.
ConAgra Foods Inc.
Concord EFS Inc.
"Conectiv, Inc"
Conoco Inc
Conseco Inc.
Consolidated Freightways Corp.
Consolidated Edison Inc.
Constellation Brands Inc.
Constellation Emergy Group Inc.
Continental Airlines Inc.
Convergys Corp.
Cooper Cameron Corp.
Cooper Industries Ltd.
Cooper Tire & Rubber Co.
Corn Products International Inc.
Corning Inc.
Costco Wholesale Corp.
Countrywide Credit Industries Inc.
Coventry Health Care Inc.
Cox Communications Inc.
Crane Co.
Crompton Corp.
Crown Cork & Seal Co. Inc.
CSK Auto Corp.
CSX Corp.
Cummins Inc.
CVS Corp.
Cytec Industries Inc.
"D&K Healthcare Resources, Inc."
D.R. Horton Inc.
Dana Corporation
Danaher Corporation
Darden Restaurants Inc.
DaVita Inc.
Dean Foods Company
Deere & Company
Del Monte Foods Co
Dell Computer Corporation
Delphi Corp.
Delta Air Lines Inc.
Deluxe Corporation
Devon Energy Corporation
Di Giorgio Corporation
Dial Corporation
Diebold Incorporated
Dillard's Inc.
DIMON Incorporated
"Dole Food Company, Inc."
Dollar General Corporation
"Dollar Tree Stores, Inc."
"Dominion Resources, Inc."
Domino's Pizza LLC
"Dover Corporation, Inc."
Dow Chemical Company
"Dow Jones & Company, Inc."
DPL Inc.
DQE Inc.
"Dreyer's Grand Ice Cream, Inc."
"DST Systems, Inc."
DTE Energy Co.
E.I. Du Pont de Nemours and Company
Duke Energy Corp
Dun & Bradstreet Inc.
DURA Automotive Systems Inc.
DynCorp
Dynegy Inc.
"E*Trade Group, Inc."
E.W. Scripps Company
"Earthlink, Inc."
Eastman Chemical Company
Eastman Kodak Company
Eaton Corporation
Echostar Communications Corporation
Ecolab Inc.
Edison International
EGL Inc.
El Paso Corporation
Electronic Arts Inc.
Electronic Data Systems Corp.
Eli Lilly and Company
EMC Corporation
Emcor Group Inc.
Emerson Electric Co.
Encompass Services Corporation
Energizer Holdings Inc.
Energy East Corporation
Engelhard Corporation
Enron Corp.
Entergy Corporation
Enterprise Products Partners L.P.
"EOG Resources, Inc."
Equifax Inc.
Equitable Resources Inc.
Equity Office Properties Trust
Equity Residential Properties Trust
Estee Lauder Companies Inc.
Exelon Corporation
Exide Technologies
Expeditors International of Washington Inc.
Express Scripts Inc.
ExxonMobil Corporation
Fairchild Semiconductor International Inc.
Family Dollar Stores Inc.
Farmland Industries Inc.
Federal Mogul Corp.
Federated Department Stores Inc.
Federal Express Corp.
Felcor Lodging Trust Inc.
Ferro Corp.
Fidelity National Financial Inc.
Fifth Third Bancorp
First American Financial Corp.
First Data Corp.
First National of Nebraska Inc.
First Tennessee National Corp.
FirstEnergy Corp.
Fiserv Inc.
Fisher Scientific International Inc.
FleetBoston Financial Co.
Fleetwood Enterprises Inc.
Fleming Companies Inc.
Flowers Foods Inc.
Flowserv Corp
Fluor Corp
FMC Corp
Foamex International Inc
Foot Locker Inc
Footstar Inc.
Ford Motor Co
Forest Laboratories Inc.
Fortune Brands Inc.
Foster Wheeler Ltd.
FPL Group Inc.
Franklin Resources Inc.
Freeport McMoran Copper & Gold Inc.
Frontier Oil Corp
Furniture Brands International Inc.
"Gannett Co., Inc."
Gap Inc.
Gateway Inc.
GATX Corporation
Gemstar-TV Guide International Inc.
GenCorp Inc.
General Cable Corporation
General Dynamics Corporation
General Electric Company
General Mills Inc
General Motors Corporation
Genesis Health Ventures Inc.
Gentek Inc.
Gentiva Health Services Inc.
Genuine Parts Company
Genuity Inc.
Genzyme Corporation
Georgia Gulf Corporation
Georgia-Pacific Corporation
Gillette Company
Gold Kist Inc.
Golden State Bancorp Inc.
Golden West Financial Corporation
Goldman Sachs Group Inc.
Goodrich Corporation
The Goodyear Tire & Rubber Company
Granite Construction Incorporated
Graybar Electric Company Inc.
Great Lakes Chemical Corporation
Great Plains Energy Inc.
GreenPoint Financial Corp.
Greif Bros. Corporation
Grey Global Group Inc.
Group 1 Automotive Inc.
Guidant Corporation
H&R Block Inc.
H.B. Fuller Company
H.J. Heinz Company
Halliburton Co.
Harley-Davidson Inc.
Harman International Industries Inc.
Harrah's Entertainment Inc.
Harris Corp.
Harsco Corp.
Hartford Financial Services Group Inc.
Hasbro Inc.
Hawaiian Electric Industries Inc.
HCA Inc.
Health Management Associates Inc.
Health Net Inc.
Healthsouth Corp
Henry Schein Inc.
Hercules Inc.
Herman Miller Inc.
Hershey Foods Corp.
Hewlett-Packard Company
Hibernia Corp.
Hillenbrand Industries Inc.
Hilton Hotels Corp.
Hollywood Entertainment Corp.
Home Depot Inc.
Hon Industries Inc.
Honeywell International Inc.
Hormel Foods Corp.
Host Marriott Corp.
Household International Corp.
Hovnanian Enterprises Inc.
Hub Group Inc.
Hubbell Inc.
Hughes Supply Inc.
Humana Inc.
Huntington Bancshares Inc.
Idacorp Inc.
IDT Corporation
IKON Office Solutions Inc.
Illinois Tool Works Inc.
IMC Global Inc.
Imperial Sugar Company
IMS Health Inc.
Ingles Market Inc
Ingram Micro Inc.
Insight Enterprises Inc.
Integrated Electrical Services Inc.
Intel Corporation
International Paper Co.
Interpublic Group of Companies Inc.
Interstate Bakeries Corporation
International Business Machines Corp.
International Flavors & Fragrances Inc.
International Multifoods Corporation
Intuit Inc.
IT Group Inc.
ITT Industries Inc.
Ivax Corp.
J.B. Hunt Transport Services Inc.
J.C. Penny Co.
J.P. Morgan Chase & Co.
Jabil Circuit Inc.
Jack In The Box Inc.
Jacobs Engineering Group Inc.
JDS Uniphase Corp.
Jefferson-Pilot Co.
John Hancock Financial Services Inc.
Johnson & Johnson
Johnson Controls Inc.
Jones Apparel Group Inc.
KB Home
Kellogg Company
Kellwood Company
Kelly Services Inc.
Kemet Corp.
Kennametal Inc.
Kerr-McGee Corporation
KeyCorp
KeySpan Corp.
Kimball International Inc.
Kimberly-Clark Corporation
Kindred Healthcare Inc.
KLA-Tencor Corporation
K-Mart Corp.
Knight-Ridder Inc.
Kohl's Corp.
KPMG Consulting Inc.
Kroger Co.
L-3 Communications Holdings Inc.
Laboratory Corporation of America Holdings
Lam Research Corporation
LandAmerica Financial Group Inc.
Lands' End Inc.
Landstar System Inc.
La-Z-Boy Inc.
Lear Corporation
Legg Mason Inc.
Leggett & Platt Inc.
Lehman Brothers Holdings Inc.
Lennar Corporation
Lennox International Inc.
Level 3 Communications Inc.
Levi Strauss & Co.
Lexmark International Inc.
Limited Inc.
Lincoln National Corporation
Linens 'n Things Inc.
Lithia Motors Inc.
Liz Claiborne Inc.
Lockheed Martin Corporation
Loews Corporation
Longs Drug Stores Corporation
Louisiana-Pacific Corporation
Lowe's Companies Inc.
LSI Logic Corporation
The LTV Corporation
The Lubrizol Corporation
Lucent Technologies Inc.
Lyondell Chemical Company
M & T Bank Corporation
Magellan Health Services Inc.
Mail-Well Inc.
Mandalay Resort Group
Manor Care Inc.
Manpower Inc.
Marathon Oil Corporation
Mariner Health Care Inc.
Markel Corporation
Marriott International Inc.
Marsh & McLennan Companies Inc.
Marsh Supermarkets Inc.
Marshall & Ilsley Corporation
Martin Marietta Materials Inc.
Masco Corporation
Massey Energy Company
MasTec Inc.
Mattel Inc.
Maxim Integrated Products Inc.
Maxtor Corporation
Maxxam Inc.
The May Department Stores Company
Maytag Corporation
MBNA Corporation
McCormick & Company Incorporated
McDonald's Corporation
The McGraw-Hill Companies Inc.
McKesson Corporation
McLeodUSA Incorporated
M.D.C. Holdings Inc.
MDU Resources Group Inc.
MeadWestvaco Corporation
Medtronic Inc.
Mellon Financial Corporation
The Men's Wearhouse Inc.
"Merck & Co., Inc."
Mercury General Corporation
Merrill Lynch & Co. Inc.
Metaldyne Corporation
Metals USA Inc.
MetLife Inc.
Metris Companies Inc
MGIC Investment Corporation
MGM Mirage
Michaels Stores Inc.
Micron Technology Inc.
Microsoft Corporation
Milacron Inc.
Millennium Chemicals Inc.
Mirant Corporation
Mohawk Industries Inc.
Molex Incorporated
The MONY Group Inc.
Morgan Stanley Dean Witter & Co.
Motorola Inc.
MPS Group Inc.
Murphy Oil Corporation
Nabors Industries Inc
Nacco Industries Inc
Nash Finch Company
National City Corp.
National Commerce Financial Corporation
National Fuel Gas Company
National Oilwell Inc
National Rural Utilities Cooperative Finance Corporation
National Semiconductor Corporation
National Service Industries Inc
Navistar International Corporation
NCR Corporation
The Neiman Marcus Group Inc.
New Jersey Resources Corporation
New York Times Company
Newell Rubbermaid Inc
Newmont Mining Corporation
Nextel Communications Inc
Nicor Inc
Nike Inc
NiSource Inc
Noble Energy Inc
Nordstrom Inc
Norfolk Southern Corporation
Nortek Inc
North Fork Bancorporation Inc
Northeast Utilities System
Northern Trust Corporation
Northrop Grumman Corporation
NorthWestern Corporation
Novellus Systems Inc
NSTAR
NTL Incorporated
Nucor Corp
Nvidia Corp
NVR Inc
Northwest Airlines Corp
Occidental Petroleum Corp
Ocean Energy Inc
Office Depot Inc.
OfficeMax Inc
OGE Energy Corp
Oglethorpe Power Corp.
Ohio Casualty Corp.
Old Republic International Corp.
Olin Corp.
OM Group Inc
Omnicare Inc
Omnicom Group
On Semiconductor Corp
ONEOK Inc
Oracle Corp
Oshkosh Truck Corp
Outback Steakhouse Inc.
Owens & Minor Inc.
Owens Corning
Owens-Illinois Inc
Oxford Health Plans Inc
Paccar Inc
PacifiCare Health Systems Inc
Packaging Corp. of America
Pactiv Corp
Pall Corp
Pantry Inc
Park Place Entertainment Corp
Parker Hannifin Corp.
Pathmark Stores Inc.
Paychex Inc
Payless Shoesource Inc
Penn Traffic Co.
Pennzoil-Quaker State Company
Pentair Inc
Peoples Energy Corp.
PeopleSoft Inc
"Pep Boys Manny, Moe & Jack"
Potomac Electric Power Co.
Pepsi Bottling Group Inc.
PepsiAmericas Inc.
PepsiCo Inc.
Performance Food Group Co.
Perini Corp
PerkinElmer Inc
Perot Systems Corp
Petco Animal Supplies Inc.
"Peter Kiewit Sons', Inc."
PETsMART Inc
Pfizer Inc
Pacific Gas & Electric Corp.
Pharmacia Corp
Phar Mor Inc.
Phelps Dodge Corp.
Philip Morris Companies Inc.
Phillips Petroleum Co
Phillips Van Heusen Corp.
Phoenix Companies Inc
Pier 1 Imports Inc.
Pilgrim's Pride Corporation
Pinnacle West Capital Corp
Pioneer-Standard Electronics Inc.
Pitney Bowes Inc.
Pittston Brinks Group
Plains All American Pipeline LP
PNC Financial Services Group Inc.
PNM Resources Inc
Polaris Industries Inc.
Polo Ralph Lauren Corp
PolyOne Corp
Popular Inc
Potlatch Corp
PPG Industries Inc
PPL Corp
Praxair Inc
Precision Castparts Corp
Premcor Inc.
Pride International Inc
Primedia Inc
Principal Financial Group Inc.
Procter & Gamble Co.
Pro-Fac Cooperative Inc.
Progress Energy Inc
Progressive Corporation
Protective Life Corp
Provident Financial Group
Providian Financial Corp.
Prudential Financial Inc.
PSS World Medical Inc
Public Service Enterprise Group Inc.
Publix Super Markets Inc.
Puget Energy Inc.
Pulte Homes Inc
Qualcomm Inc
Quanta Services Inc.
Quantum Corp
Quest Diagnostics Inc.
Questar Corp
Quintiles Transnational
Qwest Communications Intl Inc
R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company
R.R. Donnelley & Sons Company
Radio Shack Corporation
Raymond James Financial Inc.
Raytheon Company
Reader's Digest Association Inc.
Reebok International Ltd.
Regions Financial Corp.
Regis Corporation
Reliance Steel & Aluminum Co.
Reliant Energy Inc.
Rent A Center Inc
Republic Services Inc
Revlon Inc
RGS Energy Group Inc
Rite Aid Corp
Riverwood Holding Inc.
RoadwayCorp
Robert Half International Inc.
Rock-Tenn Co
Rockwell Automation Inc
Rockwell Collins Inc
Rohm & Haas Co.
Ross Stores Inc
RPM Inc.
Ruddick Corp
Ryder System Inc
Ryerson Tull Inc
Ryland Group Inc.
Sabre Holdings Corp
Safeco Corp
Safeguard Scientifics Inc.
Safeway Inc
Saks Inc
Sanmina-SCI Inc
Sara Lee Corp
SBC Communications Inc
Scana Corp.
Schering-Plough Corp
Scholastic Corp
SCI Systems Onc.
Science Applications Intl. Inc.
Scientific-Atlanta Inc
Scotts Company
Seaboard Corp
Sealed Air Corp
Sears Roebuck & Co
Sempra Energy
Sequa Corp
Service Corp. International
ServiceMaster Co
Shaw Group Inc
Sherwin-Williams Company
Shopko Stores Inc
Siebel Systems Inc
Sierra Health Services Inc
Sierra Pacific Resources
Silgan Holdings Inc.
Silicon Graphics Inc
Simon Property Group Inc
SLM Corporation
Smith International Inc
Smithfield Foods Inc
Smurfit-Stone Container Corp
Snap-On Inc
Solectron Corp
Solutia Inc
Sonic Automotive Inc.
Sonoco Products Co.
Southern Company
Southern Union Company
SouthTrust Corp.
Southwest Airlines Co
Southwest Gas Corp
Sovereign Bancorp Inc.
Spartan Stores Inc
Spherion Corp
Sports Authority Inc
Sprint Corp.
SPX Corp
St. Jude Medical Inc
St. Paul Cos.
Staff Leasing Inc.
StanCorp Financial Group Inc
Standard Pacific Corp.
Stanley Works
Staples Inc
Starbucks Corp
Starwood Hotels & Resorts Worldwide Inc
State Street Corp.
Stater Bros. Holdings Inc.
Steelcase Inc
Stein Mart Inc
Stewart & Stevenson Services Inc
Stewart Information Services Corp
Stilwell Financial Inc
Storage Technology Corporation
Stryker Corp
Sun Healthcare Group Inc.
Sun Microsystems Inc.
SunGard Data Systems Inc.
Sunoco Inc.
SunTrust Banks Inc
Supervalu Inc
"Swift Transportation, Co., Inc"
Symbol Technologies Inc
Synovus Financial Corp.
Sysco Corp
Systemax Inc.
Target Corp.
Tech Data Corporation
TECO Energy Inc
Tecumseh Products Company
Tektronix Inc
Teleflex Incorporated
Telephone & Data Systems Inc
Tellabs Inc.
Temple-Inland Inc
Tenet Healthcare Corporation
Tenneco Automotive Inc.
Teradyne Inc
Terex Corp
Tesoro Petroleum Corp.
Texas Industries Inc.
Texas Instruments Incorporated
Textron Inc
Thermo Electron Corporation
Thomas & Betts Corporation
Tiffany & Co
Timken Company
TJX Companies Inc
TMP Worldwide Inc
Toll Brothers Inc
Torchmark Corporation
Toro Company
Tower Automotive Inc.
Toys 'R' Us Inc
Trans World Entertainment Corp.
TransMontaigne Inc
Transocean Inc
TravelCenters of America Inc.
Triad Hospitals Inc
Tribune Company
Trigon Healthcare Inc.
Trinity Industries Inc
Trump Hotels & Casino Resorts Inc.
TruServ Corporation
TRW Inc
TXU Corp
Tyson Foods Inc
U.S. Bancorp
U.S. Industries Inc.
UAL Corporation
UGI Corporation
Unified Western Grocers Inc
Union Pacific Corporation
Union Planters Corp
Unisource Energy Corp
Unisys Corporation
United Auto Group Inc
United Defense Industries Inc.
United Parcel Service Inc
United Rentals Inc
United Stationers Inc
United Technologies Corporation
UnitedHealth Group Incorporated
Unitrin Inc
Universal Corporation
Universal Forest Products Inc
Universal Health Services Inc
Unocal Corporation
Unova Inc
UnumProvident Corporation
URS Corporation
US Airways Group Inc
US Oncology Inc
USA Interactive
USFreighways Corporation
USG Corporation
UST Inc
Valero Energy Corporation
Valspar Corporation
Value City Department Stores Inc
Varco International Inc
Vectren Corporation
Veritas Software Corporation
Verizon Communications Inc
VF Corporation
Viacom Inc
Viad Corp
Viasystems Group Inc
Vishay Intertechnology Inc
Visteon Corporation
Volt Information Sciences Inc
Vulcan Materials Company
W.R. Berkley Corporation
W.R. Grace & Co
W.W. Grainger Inc
Wachovia Corporation
Wakenhut Corporation
Walgreen Co
Wallace Computer Services Inc
Wal-Mart Stores Inc
Walt Disney Co
Walter Industries Inc
Washington Mutual Inc
Washington Post Co.
Waste Management Inc
Watsco Inc
Weatherford International Inc
Weis Markets Inc.
Wellpoint Health Networks Inc
Wells Fargo & Company
Wendy's International Inc
Werner Enterprises Inc
WESCO International Inc
Western Digital Inc
Western Gas Resources Inc
WestPoint Stevens Inc
Weyerhauser Company
WGL Holdings Inc
Whirlpool Corporation
Whole Foods Market Inc
Willamette Industries Inc.
Williams Companies Inc
Williams Sonoma Inc
Winn Dixie Stores Inc
Wisconsin Energy Corporation
Wm Wrigley Jr Company
World Fuel Services Corporation
WorldCom Inc
Worthington Industries Inc
WPS Resources Corporation
Wyeth
Wyndham International Inc
Xcel Energy Inc
Xerox Corp
Xilinx Inc
XO Communications Inc
Yellow Corporation
York International Corp
Yum Brands Inc.
Zale Corporation
Zions Bancorporation